The first thing you'll want to do is get
首先需要能访问
access to the notebooks that we'll be using in this lesson.
我们将在这节课使用的 notebook
I'm assuming that you've gone through this process
我假设你之前已经完成了这个流程
before and already have an AWS account.
并且已经有 AWS 帐户
So I've already logged into my AWS console here.
我已经登录了 AWS 控制台
I'll just quickly go through getting to
下面快速讲解下如何通过
the SageMaker console and creating a notebook instance.
SageMaker 控制台创建 notebook 实例
It never hurts to practice,
练习一遍没有坏处
and this dashboard occasionally changes in appearance.
并且这个信息中心总是时不时地变化
So this is what it looks like as I'm going through this exercise.
在我讲解这道练习时 界面是这样的
I've logged into my personal AWS account, and I have my region,
我登录了我的 AWS 帐户 我所在的区域是
which is in Northern California,
北加州
and you should set this for yourself as well.
你自己也可以设置一下
Then I want to get to Amazon SageMaker,
我要打开 Amazon SageMaker
and I can just search for it by name.
可以直接搜索名称
So here's the SageMaker dashboard.
这是 SageMaker 信息中心
You can see a lot of buttons on the side that point to things like notebook instances,
左侧有很多按钮 指向各种不同的工具
training jobs, as well as things like models and end points,
例如 notebook 实例 训练作业以及模型和端点
which will be useful for monitoring how our models train later.
稍后可以使用它监控模型的运行状况
For now I want to actually create a new notebook instance.
现在我要创建一个新的 notebook 实例
So I'm going to click on this button.
点击这个按钮
Now I actually have a couple of notebooks that I'm in the middle of working with,
这里有几个我正在处理的 notebook
but it's okay if this is blank or looks a bit different for you.
如果你的这里为空 或者看起来不一样也没关系
We'll be working with a completely new notebook anyways.
反正我们将处理一个完全新的 notebook
So to create a new notebook I'm going to click
要创建新的 notebook 点击这个按钮
this button up here, Create notebook instance.
“Create notebook instance”
You should see this pop-up,
你将看到这样的弹出式窗口
a place to specify in my notebook instance settings.
可以在其中指定 notebook 实例设置
First I need to add a name for my notebook.
首先需要命名 notebook
You can call this whatever you like and only mean something descriptive,
你可以随意命名 我将设置一个描述性名称
like ML case studies.
例如 ML_Case_Studies
For many of the rest of these values,
剩下的很多值
you can leave them as the default value.
可以保留为默认值
For example the instance type is ml.t2 medium,
例如实例类型是 ml.t2 medium
which is a CPU instance that's going to be ideal for a development environment.
它是一个 CPU 实例 很适合开发环境
Next there's the IAM role.
接着是 IAM 角色
In small print, you can see a description of this role.
在下面的小号文字中可以看到这个角色的说明
It says, Choose a role or let us create a role with
内容是“选择一个角色或创建一个角色
the AmazonSageMakerFullAccess IAM policy attached.
并且具有 AmazonSageMakerFullAccess IAM 策略”
This role defines the permissions that your notebook has,
这个角色定义了 notebook 具有的权限
like what data it can read or write,
例如可以读写什么数据
and a full access role will give us access to all the public data-sets in S3 for example.
完整权限角色可以访问 S3 上的所有公共数据集
I'd suggest you click this and select Create a new role.
建议点击这个并选择“Create a new role”
Here you can see that by default,
从这里你可以看出 默认情况下
you have access to any S3 bucket with SageMaker in the name,
你可以访问名称中带有 SageMaker 的任何 S3 存储桶
and we can also specify any additional buckets.
还可以指定其他存储桶
But for these examples, we won't have any.
但是对于这些示例来说 我们没有任何其他存储桶
So you can select None here and then click Create role to complete a new role.
所以这里选择“None” 然后点击“Create role”创建一个新角色
Okay, so we have an instance name,
我们设定了实例名称和类型
we have a type, and we have a new role that we just created.
并且刚刚创建了新的角色
Now for VPC, life cycle,
对于 VPC 生命周期
encryption and volume size,
加密和容量大小
you can leave these as the default values.
可以保留为默认值
Now you could create an empty notebook instance right now.
你可以立即创建一个空的 notebook 实例了
But we'll actually want to link this to a Git repository,
但是我们将关联到 Git 代码库
and we can do that with this tab here.
点击这个标签
I want to link this notebook to a public Git repository.
我希望将此 notebook 关联到公共 Git 代码库
Specifically, I want to clone the lesson notebooks that are in
我要克隆位于优达学城公共代码库里的课程 notebook
a Udacity public repository called ML SageMaker Studies,
这个代码库称为 ML_SageMaker_Studies
and I can link to it by name.
我可以通过名称关联该代码库
This repository holds examples for a bunch of lessons,
这个代码库里存储了多个课程的示例
and so I just need to create this one notebook instance to work through all of them.
所以只需创建一个 notebook 实例就能讲解所有这些示例
The last thing I need to do is just click Create notebook instance.
最后点击“Create notebook instance”
Then you should get back to this main notebook instance page,
然后转到这个 notebook 实例主页面
and you should see that your notebook is in pending status.
可以看到该 notebook 处于 pending 状态
I actually deleted one of my older notebooks
我实际上删除了我之前的 notebook
to make room for this new ML case studies one.
从而为这个 notebook 腾出空间
It may take a moment for this to become in service,
可能需要一段时间这个 notebook 才能处于 InService状态
but once it does, you can select to open it in Jupyter or Jupyter lab.
处于 InService 状态后 可以选择以 Jupyter 或 JupyterLab 形式打开
I find Jupyter lab to be most helpful when you're
我发现如果要在不同的文件之间来回切换
moving back and forth between files often,
JupyterLab 最有用
as you might in larger projects.
大型项目就需要来回切换文件
But for these example notebooks,
但是对于这些示例 notebook 来说
I'm just going to work in Jupyter.
我将直接用 Jupyter 打开
When you open this notebook instance you should see all files
打开此 notebook 实例后
that were in the GitHub repository for ML SageMaker studies.
应该会看到 ML_SageMaker_Studies GitHub 代码库中的所有文件
These are all the lessons and examples that we'll be going through.
我们将学习所有这些课程和示例
I suggest you create a notebook instance of your own and have that open in one tab,
建议你也创建一个 notebook 实例并在学习这些课程的过程中
while going through these lessons,
在一个标签页中打开该实例
that way you can alternate between learning and applying what you've learned.
这样就可以一边学习 一边运用所学的知识
For the first lesson I'll be working with the population segmentation directory.
在第一节课 我们将打开 Population_Segmentation 目录
Tasks and exercises are presented to you in the pop segmentation exercise notebook.
Pop_Segmentation_Exercise notebook 中包含任务和练习
If you need a place to consult a final solution,
如果你想参考最终解决方案
you can look at the solution notebook.
可以查看解答 notebook
So to work through this lesson,
对于这节课
I'm going to click on this exercise notebook.
我将点击这个练习 notebook
All right. Next, I'll go over the task of
好的接下来我将介绍
population segmentation and start loading and
人口细分练习的任务并开始加载和探索
exploring the data we'll be working with in this exercise notebook.
在此练习 notebook 中将用到的数据